collection title
undated
temp2018-09-12T14:26
99 Linear feet
- Series 2: Community Theater Productions
  - Scrapbook 1: Chico Community Little Theater/Tahoe Little Theater/Lake Tahoe Children's Theater, 1960-1977; NC1338_2_1 (Box 17, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 2: Lake Tahoe Children's Theater, 1961-1972; NC1338_2_2 (Box 18, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 3: Lake Tahoe Children's Theater, 1960-1977; NC1338_2_3 (Box 19, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 4: South Lake Tahoe Theater Company, 1980-1981; NC1338_2_4 (Box 20, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 5: Santa Rosa theater productions, 1979-1985; NC1338_2_5 (Box 21, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 6: Santa Rosa theater productions, 1986-1992; NC1338_2_6 (Box 22, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook 7: Santa Rosa theater productions, 1991-1999; NC1338_2_7 (Box 23, Volume 1)
  - CD: Children's Theater, undated; NC1338_2_8 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - CD: Straw Hat production, undated; NC1338_2_9 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - CD: Kurt Weill's "All You Need", "Gopher's Breath" (includes back up with "Straw Hat"), May 2006; NC1338_2_10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - CD: Kurt Weill's "Actors Theater", October 2001; NC1338_2_11 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - CD: Kurt Weill's "Cabaret", undated; NC1338_2_12 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - VHS: Kurt Weill's "Cabaret", undated; NC1338_2_13 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Umatic VHS: "Sentimental Journey: Music and Words of World War II", 1994; NC1338_2_14 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cassette: "Sentimental Journey", December 17, 1994; NC1338_2_15 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Sentimental Journey" newspaper advertisement (copy), July 1, 1999; NC1338_2_16 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - CD: Betty Cole Graham's "Mad About Movies" and "Sentimental Journey", 1994; 2003; NC1338_2_17 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - CD: Betty Cole Graham's "Mad About Movies", September 2003; NC1338_2_18 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "Mad About Movies" promotional material, 2003; NC1338_2_19 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - CD: Betty Cole Graham's "Show Biz", 2005; NC1338_2_20 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "Dames at Sea" photographs, undated; NC1338_2_21 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "Mame" cast photograph, 1989; NC1338_2_22 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - CD: Betty Cole Graham demo reels, undated; NC1338_2_23 (Box 24, Folder 15)